{
"question": "然うして",
"answer": "そうして"
},
{
"question": "瓦",
"answer": "グラム"
},
{
"question": "瓩",
"answer": "キログラム"
},
{
"question": "直ぐに",
"answer": "すぐに"
},
{
"question": "一月-1",
"answer": "ひとつき"
},
{
"question": "あのう",
"answer": "あの"
},
{
"question": "秋",
"answer": "あき"
},
{
"question": "字引",
"answer": "じびき"
},
{
"question": "咖哩",
"answer": "カレー"
},
{
"question": "バス",
"answer": "バス"
},
{
"question": "三-1",
"answer": "サン"
},
{
"question": "コート",
"answer": "コート"
},
{
"question": "コップ",
"answer": "コップ"
},
{
"question": "フォーク",
"answer": "フォーク"
},
{
"question": "ラジカセ",
"answer": "ラジカセ"
},
{
"question": "マッチ",
"answer": "マッチ"
},
{
"question": "ＰＥＴ",
"answer": "ペット"
},
{
